{
    "id": "089cf4bb3dd845669929e051e4c82459",
    "title": "Sentence Synthesis Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James plays hockey .................................... cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well",
                "also",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "07f8b55db99c4ee8a8408fece7cf54e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be asleep ........................................... there is no light in his room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ade26f40e9d441cb2e6739e853fe9ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks Hindi .................................... English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "as well",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f8d05811914e420ba882f68689c977fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter is quite sociable ........................................ his brother is rather reserved.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "as",
                "whereas"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "473b1e5cf5954f30bc30d0b39a102c39"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was little hope of success, ................................... I tried hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "as",
                "nevertheless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "34e619d2be8a4ab8ae82b03ae02faff5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will neither spend his money ........................................ invest it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor",
                "either"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f949ff819aad4c0cb1e4785057c1fb53"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ...................................... a fool or a madman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9135d0d50c13406f92d131c4c139161e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been working hard, ..................................... he will pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "therefore",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "661672bddac54ef0bd52dca3c3da9fb4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did my best, ......................................... I failed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "but",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dae6e4c17ee34cc6abdda4ebfe3e176b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The way was long ..................................... the wind was cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb5644e10ff84b0abddf5250f8c75dc5"
        }
    ]
}